http://www.rosedalefederal.com/privacy-policy

Skip Navigation Documents in Portable Document Format (PDF) require Adobe Acrobat Reader 5.0 or higher to view,download Adobe® Acrobat Reader.
Calculators
Search Query:
MenuToggle navigation
Privacy Policy
Rev. 1/2019
FACTS
What Do We Do With Your Personal Information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security Number and Income
Account Balances and Payment History
Credit History and Credit Scores
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Rosedale Federal Savings & Loan Association chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Rosedale Federal share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
YES
NO
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
YES
NO
For joint marketing with other financial companies
YES
NO
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences
NO
We don't share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
NO
We don't share
For our affiliates to market to you -
NO
We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you –
NO
We don't share
Questions?
Call 410-668-4400 or go to www.rosedalefederal.com
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
This notice is being provided by Rosedale Federal Savings & Loan Association.
What we do
How does Rosedale Federal protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Rosedale Federal collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit money
pay your bills or apply for a loan
use your debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Rosedale Federal has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Rosedale Federal does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include credit card companies.
